<resources>
    <string name="app_name">PixelNut!</string>
    <string name="my_name">Greg de Valois</string>
    <string name="name_website">Website</string>
    <string name="name_stop">Stop</string>
    <string name="name_scan">Scan</string>
    <string name="name_wait">Wait</string>
    <string name="name_done">Done</string>
    <string name="name_cancel">Cancel</string>
    <string name="name_continue">Continue</string>
    <string name="name_help">\?</string>
    <string name="name_pause">Pause</string>
    <string name="name_resume">Resume</string>
    <string name="name_disable">Disable</string>
    <string name="name_enable">Enable</string>
    <string name="name_trigger">Trigger</string>
    <string name="title_copyright">Copyright 2020</string>
    <string name="title_allrights">All rights reserved</string>
    <string name="title_select">Select A PixelNut Device</string>
    <string name="title_connecting">Connecting…</string>
    <string name="title_configuring">Configuring…</string>
    <string name="title_segments">Select segment to control</string>
    <string name="title_pattern">Choose effect pattern</string>
    <string name="title_adjust">Adjust brightness and speed</string>
    <string name="title_modify">Modify effect properties</string>
    <string name="title_trigforce">Select force then trigger</string>
    <string name="title_dotrigger">Press to trigger pattern</string>
    <string name="title_networks">Networks</string>
    <string name="title_help_favs">Favorites Help</string>
    <string name="title_help_ctrls">Controls Help</string>
    <string name="title_help_network">Network Help</string>
    <string name="title_favs">Favorites</string>
    <string name="action_favs">&lt;&lt;&lt; Favorites</string>
    <string name="action_ctrls_rite">Controls &gt;&gt;&gt;</string>
    <string name="text_addnetwork">
        This will clear ALL the stored network information from the device.
    </string>
    <string name="text_connectnetwork">
        This restarts the device, which then tries to connect to one of its stored networks.
        \n\nThis application will then return to the Device Scan screen.
    </string>
    <string name="text_help_head">
        You are connected to the PixelNut! device whose name is displayed in the upper left.

        \n\nYou can change this name anytime by selecting it, which opens an edit box.
        The maximum length is 16, and the only symbols allowed are: \"!#$%&amp;*-\".
        Confirm your changes by pressing Done, or it will revert back to its original name.

        \n\nAt any time you can press the Pause button to stop the animation, until you restart it with Resume.
    </string>
    <string name="text_help_favs">
        \n\nEach button shown on the Favorites page represents one particular pattern and all of its
        associated settings (brightness, speed, etc.).

        \n\nSome are built into this application, and you can also create and save your own by pressing
        the \"F\" button next to the pattern on the Controls page, after you have adjusted all of the
        controls to their desired values.

        \n\nTo remove one of these created favorites, press the \"X\" button next to the pattern on the Favorites page.
        \n
    </string>
    <string name="text_help_segs_logical">
        \n\nSelect Segment to Control:
        \n\nThese radio buttons select which segment the following controls apply to.
        Only one segment can be chosen at once, allowing for independent control of each segment.
    </string>
    <string name="text_help_segs_physical">
        \n\nSelect Segment to Control:
        \n\nThese radio buttons select which segment the following controls apply to.
        Segments normally are independently controllable unless you chain them together,
        in which case the controls apply to all the selected segments at the same time.

        \n\nPressing \"&amp;\" button enables chaining segments together, after which the segment radio buttons
        can be enabled/disabled separately. Pressing it when the button is showing \"X\" turns off chaining,
        returning independent control.
    </string>
    <string name="text_help_tail">
        \n\nChoose Effect Pattern:
        \n\nThis drop-down list allows selecting one of the built-in patterns.
        You can then modify various settings with the other controls described below.

        \n\nThe \"?\" button toggles the display of a full description of the pattern.
        The \"F\" button saves the current pattern and all of the other settings to a favorite,
        which is then displayed on the Favorites page.

        \n\nAdjust Brightness and Speed:
        \n\nThese slider controls determine the overall brightness of the pixels,
        and how fast the various animation effects change.

        \n\nModify Effect Properties:
        \n\nWhen set to Disable, the ColorHue, Whiteness, and Count properties are all determined
        from the pattern itself. In Advanced designs these properties usually change periodically.

        \n\nWhen set to Enable you can directly change them yourself with the slider controls.
        Note that some, or all, of these controls may not be active for any given pattern.

        \n\nSelect Force then Trigger:
        \n\nTriggering a pattern causes the pattern to change, depending on the pattern.
        The amount of change is determined by the amount of force that is set.

        \n\nNot all patterns allow setting the force, and some cannot be triggered at all.
        \n
    </string>
    <string name="text_help_network">
        This screen allows you to control what networks are stored in your device,
        determining how it can connect to your local WiFi network so that it can be
        controlled over the internet.

        \n\nDevices can only store up to 5 different network configurations, and can only
        be removed by clearing all of them at once.

        \n\nYou can only add networks that are currently available to the device. Use the
        Refresh button to update that list.

        \n\nBe sure to enter your private passphrase, if needed, before adding the network.

        \n\nAfter the device successfully connects to one of the networks that has been stored,
        you will no longer be able talk to the device using this application.

        \n\nInstead, use a browser and goto www.pixelnut.io/devices to connect to the device
        through the internet.
        \n
    </string>
</resources>
