<resources>
    <string name="app_name">PixelNut!</string>
    <string name="my_name">Greg de Valois</string>
    <string name="name_website">Website</string>
    <string name="name_device">Device</string>
    <string name="name_stop">Stop</string>
    <string name="name_scan">Scan</string>
    <string name="name_wait">Wait</string>
    <string name="name_done">Done</string>
    <string name="name_cancel">Cancel</string>
    <string name="name_help">Help</string>
    <string name="name_action">Action</string>
    <string name="name_pause">Pause</string>
    <string name="name_resume">Resume</string>
    <string name="name_disable">Disable</string>
    <string name="name_enable">Enable</string>
    <string name="name_trigger">Trigger</string>
    <string name="title_copyright">Copyright 2017</string>
    <string name="title_allrights">All rights reserved</string>
    <string name="title_select">Select A PixelNut Device</string>
    <string name="title_connecting">Connecting…</string>
    <string name="title_configuring">Configuring…</string>
    <string name="title_segments">Select segment to control</string>
    <string name="title_pattern">Choose effect pattern</string>
    <string name="title_adjust">Adjust brightness and speed</string>
    <string name="title_modify">Modify effect properties</string>
    <string name="title_trigforce">Select force then trigger</string>
    <string name="title_dotrigger">Press to trigger pattern</string>
    <string name="title_help_favs">Favorites Help</string>
    <string name="title_help_ctrls">Controls Help</string>
    <string name="title_favs">Favorites</string>
    <string name="action_favs">&lt;&lt;&lt; Favorites</string>
    <string name="action_ctrls_rite">Controls &gt;&gt;&gt;</string>
    <string name="action_ctrls_left">&lt;&lt;&lt; Controls</string>
    <string name="action_details">Details &gt;&gt;&gt;</string>
    <string name="text_help_head">
        These controls affect the PixelNut! device that is currently connected,
        whose name is displayed in the upper left of the screen.

        \n\nYou can change this name anytime by selecting it, which opens an edit box.
        Be sure to confirm your changes by pressing Done, or it will revert to its original name.

        \n\nAt any time you can press the Pause button to stop the animation,
        until you restart it with Resume.
    </string>
    <string name="text_help_favs">
        Help for Favorites page.
        \n\n safasdfsdf
        \n\n safasdfsdf
        \n\n safasdfsdf
        \n\n safasdfsdf
        \n\n safasdfsdf
        \n\n safasdfsdf
        \n\n safasdfsdf
        \n\n safasdfsdf
        \n\n safasdfsdf
        \n\n safasdfsdf
        \n\n safasdfsdf
        \n\n safasdfsdf
        \n\n safasdfsdf
    </string>
    <string name="text_help_tail">
        \n\nChoose Effect Pattern:
        \n\nThis drop-down list allows the selection one of the built-in patterns.
        You can then modify various setting with the other controls described below.

        \n\nThe "?" button toggles the display of a full description of the pattern.

        \n\nAdjust Brightness and Speed:
        \n\nThese slider controls determine the overall brightness of the pixels,
        and how fast the various animation effects change.

        \n\nModify Effect Properties:
        \n\nWhen set to Disable, the ColorHue, Whiteness, and Count properties are all determined
        from the pattern itself. In Advanced designs these properties usually change periodically.

        \n\nWhen set to Enable you can directly change them yourself with the slider controls.
        Note that some, or all, of these controls may not be active for any given pattern.

        \n\nSelect Force then Trigger:
        \n\nTriggering a pattern causes the pattern to change somehow, depending on the pattern.
        The amount of change is determined by the amount of force that is set with the slider.

        \n\nNot all patterns allow setting the force, and some cannot be triggered at all.
    </string>
    <string name="text_help_segs_logical">
        \n\nSelect Segment to Control:
        \n\nThese radio buttons selects the which segment the following controls apply to.
        Only one segment can be chosen at once, allowing for independent control of each segment.
    </string>
    <string name="text_help_segs_physical">
        \n\nSelect Segment to Control:
        \n\nThese radio buttons selects which segment the following controls apply to.
        Segments normally are independently controllable, unless you chain them together,
        in which case the controls apply to all the selected segments at the same time.

        \n\nPressing "&amp;" button enables chaining segments together, after which the segment radio buttons
        can be enabled/disabled separately. Pressing it when the button is showing "X" turns off chaining,
        returning independent control.
    </string>
</resources>
